itmatchonline.com 2012-09-22

# Privacy Policy of Itmatchonline.com

We respect your privacy rights and privileges. 

**Personal Information that may be collected at itmatchonline.com website**

If you elect to join itmatchonline.com, certain types of personal and company specific information will be collected, which will be shared with other users of the itmatchonline.com web site. This "basic profile" information includes your name, company name, email addresses, and/or phone and facsimile numbers and postal address. After joining, you may elect to provide optional "extended profile" information relating to your company, which will also be shared with other users of the website. 

We Will Never Sell Or Rent Your Information 

**Computer Tracking & Cookies **  
Our web sites are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our site. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to our customers 

**Transmitting Your Credit Card and Personal Information via itmatchonline.com**  
Transactions on itmatchonline.com are protected by powerful Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology (128 bit encryption), in standard use by major ecommerce web sites. SSL encrypts your credit card number, name, address, and phone number before they are sent over the Internet. 

Our web security system requires that customers use a browser that supports at least 40 bit encryption -- Netscape Navigator (version 3.0 or higher), Microsoft Internet Explorer (version 3.0 or higher), or the AOL browser (version 3.0 or higher). The use of these browsers ensures that data is authenticated and encrypted as it's transmitted. 

**Accessing Your Personnal Information**  
Any connections to our server that request personal information must be validated by a unique User ID and password that you establish during registration. 

**Your Web Session**  
itmatchonline.com creates a random session ID attached to your encrypted web connection. This encrypted session will automatically time out after 30 minutes of inactivity and you will be prompted to login again. 

**Statistical information**  
Aggregate statistical information provided by us to our advertisers or others regarding sales or website usage will not include personally identifying information 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
Changes to this policy will be posted here.
